Big Sis! Stay with me!
Big Sis!
Hey, dumbasses!
Fetch the medics!
Hey!
Sir!
Find those two, corner them,
then summon the rest of us.
Yamato, you bastard...
Page One!
You took a pretty nasty hit too.
Yeah, that was quite the punch...
Think he dislocated my jaw.
That's all?!
More importantly, where are the medics?
We're here!
You're hurting my eyes!
Pay-Pay!
It hurts ever so much!
Poor sweet little me!
Maybe you should pipe down then?
What did you say?!
Are you trying to make me cry?!
That lousy Yamato!
How dare he steal
Viceroy Kaido's Thunder Bagua?!
She's fine all right.
His is more like Blunder Bagua.
It didn't even hurt...
Big Sis...
Master Page One!
Young Master Yamato
and Straw Hat have stopped!
Okay!
Hey, Pay-Pay!
Don't leave me!
Where are you taking me?!
I don't have time for strangers!
Please wait.
I merely wish to speak.
Get out of my way!
Listen to what I have to say!
You have five seconds!
People can hear us.
Let's speak in private.
Then forget it!
Gum-Gum...
Gatling!
You stubborn jerk!
Red Hawk!
This reminds me of...
my battle against him!
Damn!
They're gone!
What's going on?
Where's Yamato?
I'm sorry!
We lost them both!
The day Kozuki Oden fell...
his stronghold, Oden Castle,
fell alongside him!
However, a group of people inside
the castle vanished into thin air!
Samurai from the Red Scabbards
and this runt!
Where did they disappear to?
To the future!
They crossed through twenty years of time...
resurfacing in the Wano of today!
They haven't aged a day!
And who exactly was responsible
for this sorcery?!
I'll tell you...
None other than Kozuki Toki!
Oden's wife, Toki, was a witch who could
send these malcontents into the future!
No way!
There are brats with topknots all over Wano!
The Kozuki name died out decades ago!
Right, brother?!
Yeah, man!
Y-You're totally right!
Yo, yo, Shogun Orochi!
Don't keep him so far from us!
Bring that brat down here!
I wanna gouge his freakin' eyes out!
How dare you call my mother a witch?!
Y-You will pay for that, Orochi!
Insolent whelp! Don't try to act tough!
How should I execute you?!
Impalement?
Shooting?
Or maybe boiling?!
What should we do, Boss?
I can't stand watching Momo like this!
The samurai will surely act.
Hold fast, Nico Robin!
Lord Momonosuke!
Though frustrated by their inability
to rescue Momonosuke,
the raiding forces have successfully
blended into the banquet!
Meanwhile, Law's submarine, the Polar Tang,
which was carrying the Red Scabbards samurai,
reached the back of the island.
Adjust trim, 38 degrees!
Adjusting, 38 degrees!
Get as close to the island as possible!
Yes, sir!
Strong currents are forming all around us!
It's the same up there.
When we surface, we'll only get one shot!
Understood!
We're counting on you, Traffy!
Bepo! Shachi! Penguin!
Are you ready?!
Aye, aye, Captain!
– Aye, aye, sir!
We're coming for you, Kaido!
All systems clear!
Ready to surface anytime!
Alright! Surface!
It's snowing...?
Room!
Shambles!
They're gone!
Close the door!
We're resubmerging!
Roger!
Rapid descent!
We're here!
That technique of yours is remarkable!
There are two entrances.
No doubt Kaido will be up there.
Hey!
Can't you be a little more gentle?!
You're asking too much!
Whose great idea was this anyway?!
Hey, wait!
That must be...
Ow, ow, ow...
Come on, mew need to be careful!
Nekomamushi!
You have grown much bigger!
Kawamatsu! You're alive!
Ashura!
You made it too!
Yeah, it's been a while!
Marco! You carried him here?!
Carrying two people really takes it out of you!
Two?!
– Izo!
Big Brother...
Big Brother!
Kiku, you have become a fine samurai.
– Izo!
You are a sight for sore eyes!
I am so glad that you came back!
I forgot to mention it before!
Marco said he knew Izo's whereabouts,
so I went there to see him!
Marco! You haven't changed one bit!
You think?
We can reminisce about
the good old days later!
Something on the sea caught my eye earlier,
so I'm gonna go check it out.
Marco! Thank you!
I'm glad I waited for twenty years.
Let's take down Kaido at any cost!
Hey, is Linlin ready yet?!
Oh, Emperor Big Mom is
already on her way here!
You should've told me that, Bao Huang!
My bad!
You can go now.
We'll make our grand announcement
alongside Momonosuke's execution!
Let's go!
All right!
A toast to celebrate this execution!
Oh, Viceroy Kaido?
Here comes Viceroy Kaido!
Listen up!
All you bastards!
Allow me to spice up this brat's dull execution.
This is... the New Onigashima Project!
Five minutes!
Years ago...
I told my father...
that I wanted to become Kozuki Oden.
Huh?!
In return, he disciplined me thoroughly.
Why are you telling me this?!
And why now of all times?!
Twenty years ago,
I witnessed Oden's execution...
the Legendary Hour.
As a samurai, he was peerless.
The ones who killed him...
were Orochi and my father...
Kaido!
It was infuriating...!
Yet, above all,
my heart was stirred. My tears flowed freely!
Later, I found this in Kuri.
Kozuki Oden's logbook.
Oh, his journal!
It's my bible!
Not even my father or his crew
know about this journal!
The pages are filled with his heroic tales
and other important tidbits.
Now that the Red Scabbards are dead,
someone has to inherit Oden's will!
That's why...
I'm going to open up this country!
You're...
Allow me to fight alongside you!
You said you were Kaido's son.
Kozuki Oden was a man, correct?
So I became a man, too.
You are incredibly strong.
I could tell you were holding back
when we fought before.
You remind me of Ace.
Wha...?!
Huh?!
I knew you would come...
There was no trace of
a samurai invasion...
but I knew deep down that
you could never stay away.
I know your tenacity better than anyone!
They're really here!
After hiding like rats
for twenty years since the boiling!
Kanjuro...
Have you betrayed us?!
Your raid ends right here.
Izo, you have returned...
just to fight this losing battle?
They're decapitated, yet still able to fight...
Nicely drawn.
They look just like you guys, don't they?!
With Oden, you lost your head, and yet
the body of the samurai writhes on.
We still have our head!
Our lord is Momonosuke!
Is Lord Momonosuke okay?!
I cannot say for certain...
He was trying the best he could to escape.
How can I get to Lord Orochi?!
Halt!
I refuse to remain a burden to them!
What are you doing?
If I let you get away...
then I cannot fulfill my role!
I only intended to knock him out...
but I overdid it a little...
Luckily, he clung on to life,
so I was able to hand him over to Lord Orochi.
Lord Momonosuke!
Any minute now, Momonosuke will
be executed on stage for all to see!
All we have to do is stop you right here.
Minutes from now, the history of
the Kozuki clan will come to an end.
Don't mess with us, Kanjuro!
Advance!
Kappa Style:
Yorikiri!
Flower Shuriken!
Go to hell!
You-gara! What happened to your leg?!
It's my two-sword style!
Isn't it cool?
It's purrific!
Now what is that?
Isn't it cool?
This will tear Kaido to shreds!
Cool...
What's wrong, Kiku?
More... Cry some more!
Come on...
Come on!
Please cease your drivel, Kanjuro.
To me, Kanjuro of the Evening Shower...
was a precious friend.
Prepare yourself.
The wounds from this blade
shall follow you to your grave.
Like the snow that remains in spring, so, too,
shall they torment your soul forevermore!
Come at me, Kiku!
Hey! Turn on the video
transponder snail already!
Kaido's speech has started!
I, as Kozuki Oden, thought that you...
as Ace's brother, would allow me
to board your ship, so I gathered info on you.
Hey!
Everyone loves Kozuki Oden!
You can't just be him!
Fine, you're more Oden than I am!
What do you mean I'm more Oden than you?!
Even if I am Oden, I'm still not free...
because of these cuffs!
I wanted to set out to sea
along with Ace and his crew...
but I've been held captive
on this island since I was eight!
Aren't those for prisoners?
Yes!
My father said they would explode
should I ever leave the island.
Honestly, I think that was probably a lie...
because what kind of a parent
would blow up their own son?!
But when I think of the worst case scenario,
I feel weak at the knees...
because my father is that kind of man.
Want me to take them off?
What?!
Do you really wanna fight alongside us?
If you come with me, I'll be kicking
Kaido's ass right in front of you!
I wish I could do it myself!
I've lost count of the beatings
he's given me since I was a child!
Every time I challenged him, I was defeated!
I see.
Okay, I'll take them off for you!
Take them off?
They've restricted my freedom
for twenty years...
It's not as easy as...
It's been two years since
the Summit War against Whitebeard!
It's footage from the Performance Floor!
The gears of the world are turning once again!
The abolition of the Seven Warlords wasn't
some act of madness by the government!
It's a sign of confidence in their ability
to bring us to heel with new
countermeasures at Marine Headquarters.
But while the World Government
wallows in ignorance,
we will gather the most
powerful forces in this world...
the ancient weapons!
To accomplish that...
we have entered into
an alliance with Big Mom!
Did I hear you...
call out my name, Kaido?
Oh, my...
Big Mom?!
Welcome back, Zeus.
Ma... ma...
Mama!
She's terrifying up close!
She's the world's strongest old hag!
Zeus!
Nami!
They were caught?!
You're finally here, Linlin!
What took you so long?!
Don't be such a stickler, Kaido!
I made it in time.
As Kaido said,
we formed an alliance with a purpose in mind!
A purpose?
If we're at each other's throats,
it's out of our reach,
but if we join hands,
it's already within our grasp!
Listen up, you louts!
We're doubling down on piracy!
At long last...
...we're going to claim...
...the great treasure
One Piece!
The One Piece...
What the heck! That's my treasure!
Those jerks!
The fear of the ancient weapons...
will ignite a terrible war across the world!
Prepare yourselves!
That is the violent world that we desire!
How exciting!
Any of you who serve Orochi, listen up!
You've got a choice to make.
A choice?
This country...
is a natural stronghold surrounded by the falls,
which makes it difficult for the Marines
and the World Government to penetrate.
If we build more weapons factories...
and force even the people
of the Flower Capital to work,
this place will become a lawless land,
a paradise for pirates!
Hey...
Hey!
Kaido, you swine!
The Flower Capital is my territory!
Do you hear me?!
For torturing the Kurozumi Clan,
I'll bring those Kozuki devils to their knees
and subject them to all manner of horrors
to keep them from rising up!
Forever and ever!
Wano is mine to destroy!
This country belongs to me!
Know your place, Kaido!
You're not even from here!
Who do you think is making it possible
for you to procure weapons?!
Wano can only exist with me!
Don't you dare forget that!
I see you understand.
What we've got to do now...
is kill that brat immedia–
I don't care!
We don't need him anymore!
Utter tripe!
To me...
both the Kurozumi Clan...
and the Kozuki Clan...
mean nothing!
Momo!
Hey, that's Momo!
Momo, wait for me!
Hey, keep it down!
Hey, what the hell?!
What's going on?!
Huh?
And now the pirate-loving fly is dead.
Those loyal to Orochi
have five seconds to decide!
Become pirates and follow me...
or challenge us right here and die?
To prepare for the coming worldwide war,
I will turn this country into a pirate empire!
We'll ramp up the expeditions
for our primary business.
So tonight,
we will relocate Onigashima
to the Flower Capital,
and Wano will fall!
That bastard!
The country's name will be New Onigashima!
And the new shogun will be my son...
Yamato!
What did he...
just say?!
You can't just force that on me!
You shitty old man!
Hurry up!
They're gonna kill Momo!
I know a shortcut!
Okay!